Guide to the Agenda Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1925-1984; Series I; 15.5; (31 boxes)
  - Clucas, Humphrey
    - "Four Poems"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 5, Folder 351)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - "Fragment, After Licinius," typescript, undated (Box 5, Folder 353)
    - "Galefucker (or Geoffrey Grigson)," typescript, undated (Box 5, Folder 354)
    - [Review] "Geographies," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 355)
    - "Gloves to the Hangman," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 356)
    - "Head Case (for P. J. D.)," typescript, with a note, undated (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - [Review] "Heath-Stubbs at Sixty," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 358)
    - "Humphrey Clucas Writes...," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 359)
    - [Review] "Levi's Psalms," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 360)
    - "Little Miss Muffet," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 361)
    - [Review] "The Luck of Palladas"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 362)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 363)
    - "Lux Aeterna," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 364)
    - "An Odd Angle"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 365)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 366)
    - [Review] "Michael Hurd: The Ordeal of Ivor Gurney," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 367)
    - [Review] "Patrick Kavanagh: Collected Poems ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 368)
    - [Review] "Peter Scupham," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 369)
    - [Review] "Peter Scupham" and "Thoth With An Accent," galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 370)
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also: Box 6, folder 378
    - [Review] Proxima Centauri by Peter Dent
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 371)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - "Sisson's Lucretius"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 373)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - [Review] "Soon Comes Night"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 375)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 376)
    - [Review] "Ted Hughes and Fay Godwin," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 377)
    - [Review] "Thoth With An Accent," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 378)
      See also: Box 6, folder 370
    - "Three Poems," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 379)
    - [Three Reviews] typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 380)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 381)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 382)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 383)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 384)
      - Galley, undated (Box 6, Folder 385)
    - [Review] Under the Penthouse, by Val Warner, typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 386)
    - [Review] "Unsatisfactory Age," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 387)
    - [Review] Urban Gorilla, by Wes Magee, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 388)
    - "Verse Drama and John Heath-Stubbs"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 389)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 389a)
    - "Versions From the Chinese," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 390)
    - "Versions of Licinius," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 391)
    - [Review] "When We Were Very Young," Hugo Williams: "Some sweet day," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 392)
    - Untitled poem, typescript, with a note, undated (Box 6, Folder 393)
  - Clucas, Humphrey, (editor)
    - "Parodies, Pastiches and Etceteras," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 394)
  - Collier, Michael
    - [Review] "Delmore"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 395)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - "Departure," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 397)
    - "Marriage Story," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 398)
    - "Traveller," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 399)
    - [Review] "Willing Sadness, Forced Joy"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 400)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 401)
  - Connolly, Cyril
    - [Review] "A Short Commentary"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 402)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 403)
  - Constable, John
    - [Review] "Derek Mahon's Development"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 404)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 6, Folder 405)
  - Cookson, William
    For additional writings see Series IV
    - "Agenda 1959-1980. A Memoir," typescript, various drafts, undated (Box 6, Folder 406)
    - [Review] "David Harsent," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 407)
    - [Review] "Donald Davie on Ezra Pound," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - "Dylan Thomas," holograph and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - [Review] "e. e. cummings," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - [Editorial] No.1, typescript, 1959 Jan (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - "Editorial," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - "Editorial," holograph and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - "Editorial," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - "Editorial," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 415)
    - [Editorial], holograph, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - [Editorial], holograph, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 417)
    - "Editorial," galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 418)
    - "Editorial," galley, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 419)
    - "Editorial," galleys, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 420)
    - "Editorial"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 421)
      - Galley, undated (Box 6, Folder 422)
    - [Review] "Ezra Pound: The Cantos ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 423)
    - [Review] "Ezra Pound: Drafts and Fragments of Cantos CX-CXVII," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 424)
    - "Ezra Pound and Myth. A Child's [Reader's] Guide to Canto II"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 425)
      - Galley, undated (Box 6, Folder 425a)
    - "Four Haikus," typescript (Box 6, Folder 426)
    - [Four Reviews], typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 427)
    - "Gists From Uncollected Prose"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 428)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 428a)
    - [Review] Michael Alexander: The Poetic Achievement of Ezra Pound, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 429)
    - [Review] The New Oxford Book of English Verse, edited by Helen Gardner, typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 430)
    - "Night Letter," galleys, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 431)
    - [Review] "A Note on Brand ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 432)
    - "Note on 'The Sleeping Lord'," holograph, undated (Box 6, Folder 433)
    - "Notes on Pound's Confuciam [sic.] Odes," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 434)
    - "Notes on the Poetry of Peter Dale," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 435)
    - "The Oldest Profession in the World," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 436)
    - "A Review," holograph, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 437)
    - "Some Notes on the Later Cantos," typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 438)
    - "Some Notes on the Poetry of Hugh MacDiarmid," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 6, Folder 439)
    - "Three Poems," typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 440)
    - "Tom Scott," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 441)
    - [Review] The Tribune's Visitation, by David Jones, holograph, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 442)
    - "Two Distinctions," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 443)
    - [Two Poems], typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 444)
    - [Two Reviews], typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 445)
    - Untitled article, holograph, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 446)
    - Untitled poem, holograph, undated (Box 7, Folder 447)
  - [Cookson, William?]
    - "Night Jar," by Mackerel Fried
      - Typescript, 2c., undated (Box 7, Folder 448)
      - Galley, undated (Box 7, Folder 449)
    - "Printer's Pie," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 450)
  - Cooper, Arthur
    - "Englishing the Earliest Chinese Poems," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 451)
    - "A Letter From Arthur Cooper," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 452)
    - "Ode LXIII," typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 453)
    - [Review] Old English Riddles, by Michael Alexander and The Exeter Book of Riddles, by Kevin Crossley-Holland
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 454)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 455)
    - "Seven Poems translated from the Chinese"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 456)
      - Galley, undated (Box 7, Folder 457)
    - "To the Leverhulme Trust Fund. Report On the Termination of Grant (1975) For 4 Years to the University of Durham For Compiling a Quick Access Dictionary of Chinese and Japanese Characters," typescript, 1980 Feb (Box 7, Folder 458)
  - Cooper, Arthur, (translator)
    - Shi King, excerpt
      - Typescript, with a note by the translator, undated (Box 7, Folder 459)
      - Galley, with translator's corrections, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 460)
        With: TLS to William Cookson from Arthur Cooper, 1975 Feb 25
  - Cooper, Joshua
    - "Three translations from the Russian"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 461)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 462)
        With: ALS to William Cookson from Joshua Cooper, 1980 Sep 4
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 463)
  - Corbière, Tristan
    - "Conlie Ditch," translated by C. H. Sisson
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 464)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 465)
    - "Two Poems," translated by Peter Dale
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 466)
      - Galley, undated (Box 7, Folder 467)
  - Corcoran, Neil
    - "Lowell Retiarius: Towards The Dolphin ," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 468)
    - [Review] "Poems Without Excuses: Some Notes on Peter Levi"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 469)
      - Galley, corrected, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 470)
  - Cory, Daniel
    - "To Ezra Pound on His 80th Birthday," typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 471)
  - Cox, D. Drew
    - "The Poet and the Architect"
      - Typescript, ca.1972 (Box 7, Folder 472)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 473)
  - Cox, Kenneth
    - [Review] "'A' 22 and 23," by Louis Zukofsky
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 474)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 7, Folder 475)
    - [Review] "'A'- 24," by Louis Zukofsky
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 476)
      - Typescript, revised draft, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 477)
    - "The Aesthetic of Mr. Basil Bunting," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 478)
    - "Allen Upward"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 479)
      - Galley, corrected, 1978 Dec 12 (Box 7, Folder 480)
    - "A Commentary on Bunting's 'Villon'"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 481)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, undated (Box 7, Folder 482)
    - "Dualism and Les Autres," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 483)
    - "New Things Seen," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 484)
    - [Review] "The Poetry of C. H. Sisson"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 485)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 7, Folder 486)
    - "The Poetry of Louis Zukofsky: A," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 487)
    - "The Poetry of Yeats and it's Place or Places Between Vision and Action," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 7, Folder 488)
    - "Zukofsky and Mallarmé: Readings in A, undated (Box 7, Folder 489)
  - Creely, Robert
    - "Corn Close," typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 490)
    - "Why Pound!?!"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 7, Folder 491)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, undated (Box 7, Folder 492)
  - Crossley-Holland, Kevin
    - "Apologia," typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 493)
    - "The Guardian Tree"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 494)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 495)
    - "Mrs. Riches," typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 496)
    - "Tertiary," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 497)
    - "Three Poems," galleys, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 498)
    - "Three Poems from Waterslain," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 499)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 500)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 501)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 502)
  - Crowhurst, Kenneth
    - "Correspondence," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 503)
  - Cumberlege, Marcus
    - "Four Centuries of Sweat (Peruvian Coastal Desert)," typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 504)
  - Dale, Peter
    - "An Apology (For R. L.)," typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 505)
    - "As Eurydice to Orpheus and Back"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 506)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 507)
    - "Basil Bunting and the Quonk and Groggle School of Poetry"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 508)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 509)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 510)
    - "Cell. A Verse-Play in One Act," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 511)
    - "Clusters"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 512)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 513)
    - [Review] Crow, by Ted Hughes, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 514)
    - "Endpapers Poetic License," galleys, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 515)
    - [Review] "Fortuitous Form," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 516)
    - "Forward"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 517)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 518)
    - [Review] " Gaudete by Ted Hughes"
      - Typescript, n.d (Box 8, Folder 519)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 520)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 521)
    - "Going Public"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 522)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, [1977?] (Box 8, Folder 523)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 524)
    - "Having No Alternative," galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 525)
    - [Review] "Instigations"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 526)
      - Galleys, undated (Box 8, Folder 527)
    - [Reviews] "Kids' Stuff," typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 528)
    - "The Months. A Group of Poems by Peter Dale," typescript, 1964 Nov (Box 8, Folder 529)
    - "No Fixed Address. A Sequence of Poems for P. C.," typescript, 1965 Apr (Box 8, Folder 530)
    - "Old Poet on a Rainy Day," typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 531)
    - "On Criticism," typescript, corrected (Box 8, Folder 532)
    - "Orpheus to Eurydice"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 533)
      - Galley, with printed version, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 534)
    - "Problems of Prosodists and Rhythm Rulers," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 535)
    - [Review] "Problems of the Short Poem"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 536)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 537)
    - [Review] "Reconsiderations," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 538)
    - "The Return"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 539)
      - Typescript, revised draft, undated (Box 8, Folder 540)
    - "Revenge for Love," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 541)
    - "Richard II Forty," typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 542)
    - [Review] "Robert Bridges," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 543)
    - "Robert Lowell," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 544)
    - [Review] " The Seamless Web by Stanley Burnshaw: A Late, Late Review," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 545)
    - "Sephe"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 8, Folder 546)
      - Typescript, carbon, 1978 Jan (Box 8, Folder 547)
      - Galley, undated (Box 8, Folder 548)
    - "Seven Sonnets"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 8, Folder 549)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 8, Folder 550)
    - "Shades," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 551)
    - "Some Idea of Sappho's Ode to Anactoria"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 552)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 553)
    - "Some translations from Jules Laforgue"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 553a)
      - "Some Translations from Jules Laforgue," galleys, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 554)
    - "Spectrum," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 555)
    - [Tamil Poetry] "Notes on the Translations," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 556)
    - "Three Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 557)
      - Galley, undated (Box 9, Folder 558)
    - "Three Sonnets from a Sequence," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 559)
    - [Review] " 23 Modern British Poets, edited by John Matthias," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 560)
    - "Two Poems," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 561)
    - "Two Poems"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 562)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 563)
    - "Unaddressed Letter," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 564)
    - Empty folder (Box 9, Folder 565)
    - "Virtue," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 566)
    - "Walk," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 567)
    - [Review] "The Waste Land"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 568)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 569)
    - "Where All the Ladders Start...," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 570)
    - "Winter," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 571)
    - "Winters," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 572)
    - Untitled article, galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 573)
  - [Dale, Peter?]
    - "'A' Level Poet's Licence: Paper One: 1976," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 574)
    - "Books Received," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 575)
    - "Books Received," by R. I. P., typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 576)
    - "Duo-Bog," by Patter Dull, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 577)
    - "Editorial," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 578)
    - "Lone Stir," by Ego Woolliambs, typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 579)
    - [Review] "The Poetic Achievement of Ezra Pound," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 580)
    - "Quiller and Couch on Westminster Bridge Again"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 581)
      - Galley, undated (Box 9, Folder 582)
    - "Reading Companions," autograph ms., undated (Box 9, Folder 583)
    - "Saving Up," by Inane Hammertone, typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 584)
    - [Review] "Verlaine," by R. I. P., typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 585)
  - Dante Alighieri
    - The Divine Comedy
      "Inferno" (unidentified translation)
      - "Canto I," typescript, p. 3-4 of an unidentified translation, undated (Box 9, Folder 586)
      - "Canto III," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 587)
      - "Purgatory," translated by C. H. Sisson
        - "Canto I," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 588)
        - "Canto II," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 589)
        - "Canto III," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 590)
    - "Cosi nel mio parlar voglio esser aspro...," translated by Tom Scott
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 591)
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 592)
      - Galleys, with translator's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 593)
    - "Sestina," translated by Peter Dale
      - Typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 594)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 595)
  - Daugherty, Michael
    - "Half and Half," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 596)
    - "September Poem," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 597)
  - Daumal, René
    - "The Poet's Last Words," translated by David Gascoyne, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 598)
  - Davenport, Guy
    - "Snow, rain, artemisia, these are the purifications," typescript, corrected, n.d (Box 9, Folder 599)
    - [Reviews] A 13-21, by Louis Zukofsky and Catullus (Gai Valeri Catulli Veronensis Liber ), by Celia and Louis Zukofsky, typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 600)
  - Davidson, Jeremy
    - "Poetry Review," typescript, corrected, with a note, undated (Box 9, Folder 601)
  - Davidson, Peter
    - [Three Poems], typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 602)
  - Davie, Donald
    - "The Blank of the Wall," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 603)
    - "Cypress Versus Rock-Slide: An Appreciation of Canto 110," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 604)
    - "England," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 605)
    - "England. A Poem"
      - First draft, typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 606)
      - Book 2, typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 607)
    - "Father, the Cavalier," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 608)
    - "Hardy's Virgilian Purples"
      - Typescript, corrected, 2c., undated (Box 9, Folder 609)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 610)
    - "In the Stopping Train"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 611)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 612)
    - "Ornithology," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 613)
    - "Reticulations"
      - Typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 614)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 615)
    - [Six Poems,] typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 616)
    - "Some notes on Rhythm in Verse," typescript, with author's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 617)
    - "Sorting the Personae"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 618)
      - Galleys, undated (Box 9, Folder 619)
    - "Three Poems," typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 620)
    - "Two Poets," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 621)
    - "The Universe of Ezra Pound"
      - Printed version, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 622)
      - Galleys, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 623)
    - "Widowers," holograph, undated
    - "A Window on 1980"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 9, Folder 624)
      - Galleys, with author's corrections, undated (Box 9, Folder 625)
  - Davis, Dick
    - [Review] "Vanishing Gardens," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 9, Folder 626)
  - Dekker, George
    - "Donald Davie: New and Divergent Lines In English Poetry"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 627)
      - Galley, corrected, undated (Box 10, Folder 628)
  - Dent, Peter
    - "Aesculus carnea," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 629)
    - "After the Greek," "Poems After the Sanskrit" and "After the Welsh," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 630)
    - "Afternoon," "Chapter," and "Pages," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 631)
    - "Alter," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 632)
    - "Beads"
      - Typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 633)
      - Galley, with author's corrections, undated (Box 10, Folder 634)
    - "Bedtime," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 635)
    - "Books Received," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 636)
    - "Call," typescript, undated (Box 10, Folder 637)